David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Research Files, circa 1750-2007 and undated; 45076; 0.520; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - Collections, circa 1750-1997 and undated; 7062; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Notebook of North Carolina Supreme Court Justice Thomas Ashe, February 1883; 29155; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notebook of North Carolina Supreme Court Justice Thomas Ashe)
    - Notebooks of North Carolina Supreme Court Justice Thomas Ruffin, Jr., February 1883; 29156; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notebooks of North Carolina Supreme Court Justice Thomas Ruffin, Jr.)
    - Notebook of North Carolina Supreme Court Justice William Smith, 1883; 29157; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notebook of North Carolina Supreme Court Justice William Smith)
    - Notes from Allen Taylor (Sealevel, N.C.) on Fishing, Including Net Diagrams, 1956; 29158; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes from Allen Taylor (Sealevel, N.C.) on Fishing, Including Net Diagrams)
    - Outer Banks Postcards, circa 1940s-1960s; 29159; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks Postcards)
    - Pamphlet: Should North Carolina Save its Cripples?, circa 1930s; 29160; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Pamphlet: Should North Carolina Save its Cripples?)
    - Papers on the Massacre of the Indians by the Turks, undated; 29161; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Papers on the Massacre of the Indians by the Turks)
    - Papers on Notable North Carolinians, 1897-1963; 29162; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Papers on Notable North Carolinians)
      Papers on Notable North Carolinians folder: Primarily consists of papers removed from a scrapbook documenting a special recognition ceremony honoring North Carolina's celebrities of the performing arts. Includes original letters and promotional photographs from Andy Griffith, David Brinkley, Ava Gardner, Betty Johnson, and John Scott Trotter. Most letters are addressed to Ted Cramer, account executive in the Office of the Governor. Also included are letters to North Carolina politicians, including a 1932 letter to Baxter Durham, State Auditor, from Amelia Earhart.
    - Picturebook of Tar Heel Authors, 1960; 29163; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Picturebook of Tar Heel Authors)
    - Political Circulars, 1806-1846; 29326; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Political Circulars)
    - Post Office Records, 1921-1947; 7064; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Colington Post Office Record, 1928-1945; 29164; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Colington Post Office Record)
      - Colington Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued, 1932-1938; 29165; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Colington Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued)
      - Colington Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued, 1938-1945; 29166; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Colington Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued)
      - Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued, 1921-1923, 1952-1927; 29167; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued)
      - Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued, 1937-1940; 29168; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued)
      - Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued, 1940-1943; 29169; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued)
      - Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued, 1945-1947; 29170; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Post Office Register of Money Orders Issued)
      - Kitty Hawk Post Office Time Record, 1946-1947; 29171; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Post Office Time Record)
      - Kitty Hawk Post Office Cash Books [3 Folders], 1942-1947; 29177; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Post Office Cash Books [3 Folders])
    - Proceedings of the First Annual North Carolina Maritime Heritage Conference, 1980; 29172; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Proceedings of the First Annual North Carolina Maritime Heritage Conference)
    - Program for Thomas Dixon's The Leopard's Spots, Wilmington Academy of Music, 16 October 1913; 29173; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Program for Thomas Dixon's The Leopard's Spots, Wilmington Academy of Music)
    - Public Welfare Institute, 1930-1954; 29174; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Public Welfare Institute)
    - Scrapbook of Rowena E Lewis (Blandford, Massachusetts), circa 1816-1852; 29175; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Scrapbook of Rowena E Lewis (Blandford, Massachusetts))
    - Seashore News, 1939; 29176; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Seashore News)
    - Shriver, August [Baltimore, Maryland area]: Diary, 1849-1859; 29178; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Shriver, August [Baltimore, Maryland area]: Diary)
    - Smith, D.J.: Notebook Containing Lecture Notes by J.W. Merrill, Professor of Theology and Philosophy at Methodist General Biblical Institute, Concord, New Hampshire, 1858; 29179; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Smith, D.J.: Notebook Containing Lecture Notes by J.W. Merrill, Professor of Theology and Philosophy at Methodist General Biblical Institute, Concord, New Hampshire)
    - Statistics of Paupers, Dare County, 1903-1904; 29327; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Statistics of Paupers, Dare County)
    - Trevanian Mills [owned by the McFadden Family, Carroll County, Maryland] Cashbook, 1891-1897; 29180; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Trevanian Mills [owned by the McFadden Family, Carroll County, Maryland] Cashbook)
    - Two Leaves from The American Colonies ("Carolina"), circa 1750; 29181; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Two Leaves from The American Colonies ("Carolina"))
    - Unidentified Account Book, 1857-1864; 29182; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Account Book)
    - Unidentified Arithmetic Exercises, circa 1800; 29183; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Arithmetic Exercises)
    - Unidentified Scrapbook, 1879-1921; 29184; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Scrapbook)
    - The University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1940-1969; 29185; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill)
    - University of North Carolina Inter-American Institute, 1941-1944; 29186; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder University of North Carolina Inter-American Institute)
    - University of North Carolina Realtor's Institute, 1967-1970; 29187; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder University of North Carolina Realtor's Institute)
    - Wilmington Taft Day Celebration Program, 9 November 1909; 29188; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wilmington Taft Day Celebration Program)
    - Womble, Brantley: Scrapbook, 1933; 29189; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Womble, Brantley: Scrapbook)
  - Subject Files, 1869-2004 and undated (bulk 1943-2004); 1943-2004; 6733; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    In addition to clippings and original manuscripts and publications, Stick created subject files on numerous topics related to eastern North Carolina history. These files generally contain Stick's notes; photocopies of materials he found in archival repositories, books, and private collections; correspondence; bibliographies; clippings; and, occasionally, original primary sources. Audiovisual materials apparently used by Stick for research purposes are also included in this subseries.
    - Albemarle-Pamlico Estuarine Study, 1987; 29190; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albemarle-Pamlico Estuarine Study)
    - Beach Nourishment, 1993; 29191; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Beach Nourishment)
    - Black People on Roanoke Island, 1999; 29192; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Black People on Roanoke Island)
    - Broadfoot, Tom, 1971-1973; 29193; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Broadfoot, Tom)
    - Cape Hatteras Lighthouse, 1998; 29194; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cape Hatteras Lighthouse)
    - Cape Hatteras Seashore, 1933-1952; 29195; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cape Hatteras Seashore)
    - Chronology: People/Events, circa 1989; 29196; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chronology: People/Events)
    - Coastal Development, 1970-1977; 29197; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Development)
    - Consolidation of Towns, 1985; 29198; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Consolidation of Towns)
    - Corps of Engineers Information on Hurricane Protection, circa 1956; 29199; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Corps of Engineers Information on Hurricane Protection)
    - Currituck County, undated; 29200; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Currituck County)
    - Cypress Pond, 1988-1994 and undated; 29201; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cypress Pond)
    - Dare County Committee Advocating Comprehensive Higher Education, 1999; 29202; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Committee Advocating Comprehensive Higher Education)
    - Dare County Standard Personnel Regulations, 1965; 29203; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Standard Personnel Regulations)
    - Dolan, Robert / Dune Stabilization, 1979-1983; 29204; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dolan, Robert / Dune Stabilization)
    - Excavations at the Amity Site, 1990; 29205; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Excavations at the Amity Site)
    - First Colony Inn Round Table Discussion [VHS], 26 October 1991; 190890; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item First Colony Inn Round Table Discussion [VHS])
    - Fort Raleigh National Historic Site, 7115; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Administrative History and Reports, circa 1966-2002; 29206; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Administrative History and Reports)
      - Brochures, 1942-1972; 29207; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Brochures)
      - Legislation Revising the Boundaries of the Fort Raleigh National Historic Site in North Carolina, 1961; 29208; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Legislation Revising the Boundaries of the Fort Raleigh National Historic Site in North Carolina)
      - National Park Service Report Recommending Purchase of Ft Raleigh Sight and Surroundings [Photocopy of 1936 document], undated; 29209; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder National Park Service Report Recommending Purchase of Ft Raleigh Sight and Surroundings [Photocopy of 1936 document])
      - Photocopied Correspondence and Memoranda from National Park Service (1938-1941), undated; 29210; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Photocopied Correspondence and Memoranda from National Park Service (1938-1941))
      - Reports: Tilberg, Stick, Porter [3 Folders], 1936-1940; 29211; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reports: Tilberg, Stick, Porter [3 Folders])
    - Gemstones, North Carolina; Minerals in North Carolina; Chemicals, 1947 and undated; 29212; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Gemstones, North Carolina; Minerals in North Carolina; Chemicals)
    - Harris, Bill, 1996-1997; 29213; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harris, Bill)
    - Harris, Bill: Tapes, etc., 1995-1997; 29214; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harris, Bill: Tapes, etc.)
    - Healthcare Materials, 1938-1943; 29215; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Healthcare Materials)
    - Hume, Ivor Noel, 1994; 29216; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hume, Ivor Noel)
    - Hurricane Research Materials, 1930s-1976; 7116; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Hurricane Audrey, 1957-1958; 29217; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Audrey)
      - Hurricane Barbara, 1953; 29218; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Barbara)
      - Hurricane Belle, August 1976; 29219; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Belle)
      - Hurricane Betsy, 1957; 29220; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Betsy)
      - Hurricane Carol, 1954-1957; 29221; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Carol)
      - Hurricane Connie, 1955-1956; 29222; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Connie)
      - Correspondence and Research Notes, 1956-1962 and undated; 29223; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence and Research Notes)
      - Dare County Hurricane Preparedness Plan, 1961; 29224; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Hurricane Preparedness Plan)
      - Hurricane Diane, 1955; 29225; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Diane)
      - Hurricane Edna, 1954; 29226; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Edna)
      - Hurricane Flossy, 1958; 29227; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Flossy)
      - Frost, Reuben L. - Record of Cape Fear Hurricanes, undated; 29228; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Frost, Reuben L. - Record of Cape Fear Hurricanes)
      - Hurricane Gracie, 1960; 29229; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Gracie)
      - Hurricane Hazel, 1954-1956; 29230; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Hazel)
      - Hurricane Helene, 1958-1959; 29231; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Helene)
      - Hurricane Biographies, 1958; 29232; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Biographies)
      - Hurricane Disasters of 1933, undated; 29233; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Disasters of 1933)
      - Hurricane Ione, 1956; 29234; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Ione)
      - Hurricane Janet, 1956; 29235; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hurricane Janet)
      - Miscellaneous Hurricane Data, 1943-1963; 29236; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Hurricane Data)
      - Newspapers: Hurricane Articles (1795, 1821, 1854), undated; 29237; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Newspapers: Hurricane Articles (1795, 1821, 1854))
      - North Atlantic Hurricane, 1944-1959; 29238; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Atlantic Hurricane)
      - North Carolina Weather Data, 1930s-1957; 29239; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Weather Data)
      - South Carolina Weather Data, 1930s-1959; 29240; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder South Carolina Weather Data)
      - Storm Data: U.S. Weather Bureau, Asheville, November 1959; 29241; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Storm Data: U.S. Weather Bureau, Asheville)
    - Items Relating to the 1974 Request to Dredge and/or Fill Areas Near the Manteo-Nags Head Causeway, undated; 29242; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Items Relating to the 1974 Request to Dredge and/or Fill Areas Near the Manteo-Nags Head Causeway)
    - Jockey's Ridge, 1998-2000; 29243; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Jockey's Ridge)
    - Kessing, Linda L., Residence, 3949 Ivy Lane (Landing Drive), Kitty Hawk, NC [VHS], 6 August 1990; 190891; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Kessing, Linda L., Residence, 3949 Ivy Lane (Landing Drive), Kitty Hawk, NC [VHS])
    - Kill Devil Hills: Matters Concerning Streets and Water Bonds, 1986-1989; 29244; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kill Devil Hills: Matters Concerning Streets and Water Bonds)
    - Kitty Hawk Bay Hunting Club, 2004; 29245; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Bay Hunting Club)
    - Kitty Hawk Historic Grove, 2002; 29246; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Historic Grove)
    - Kitty Hawk Methodist Church etc., 1958-1976; 29247; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Methodist Church etc.)
    - "Kitty Hawk" Model, 1949-1950; 29248; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder "Kitty Hawk" Model)
    - Knotts Island, 1964; 29249; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Knotts Island)
    - A List of Vessels Probably Lost on the North Carolina Coast, 1952; 29250; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder A List of Vessels Probably Lost on the North Carolina Coast)
    - Lists of Publications, 1972-1975; 29251; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lists of Publications)
    - Littleton, Tucker: Notes, 1980 and undated; 29252; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Littleton, Tucker: Notes)
    - Littleton, Tucker: Notecards on Onslow Naval History [2 folders], 1982; 29253; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Littleton, Tucker: Notecards on Onslow Naval History [2 folders])
    - Loose Research Files, 1952-1981; 29254; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Loose Research Files)
    - Loose Research Files, 1996 and undated; 29255; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Loose Research Files)
    - Maritime Forest AEC [Area of Environmental Concern], 1988-1989; 29256; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime Forest AEC [Area of Environmental Concern])
    - Maritime History Research Notes [2 Folders], 1957-1980; 29257; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime History Research Notes [2 Folders])
    - Maritime History - Spitsbergen, 1982; 29258; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maritime History - Spitsbergen)
    - Martin, Marjorie S., Residence, 3112 Bay View Drive, Kill Devil Hills [VHS], 5 August 1990; 190892; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Martin, Marjorie S., Residence, 3112 Bay View Drive, Kill Devil Hills [VHS])
    - Miscellaneous Research Notes, 1960-1964; 29259; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Research Notes)
    - Miscellaneous Research Files, 1869-1986; 29260; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Research Files)
    - Monitor [2 Folders], 1975-1979; 29261; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Monitor [2 Folders])
    - The Mullet Roar and Other Stories by William K. Brown [compact disc], undated; 190740; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item The Mullet Roar and Other Stories by William K. Brown [compact disc])
    - The Nags Head Casino: Where the Good Times Rolled, WVOD 99.1 FM [audiocassette], August 1989; 190715; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item The Nags Head Casino: Where the Good Times Rolled, WVOD 99.1 FM [audiocassette])
    - National Geographic Society, 1977-1978; 29262; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder National Geographic Society)
    - North Atlantic Right Whale, 1986; 29263; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Atlantic Right Whale)
    - North Carolina Shipwrecks Index [Folders 1-4 of 11], undated; 29264; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Shipwrecks Index [Folders 1-4 of 11])
    - North Carolina Shipwrecks Index [Folders 5-9 of 11], undated; 29265; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Shipwrecks Index [Folders 5-9 of 11])
    - North Carolina Shipwrecks Index [Folders 10-11 of 11], undated; 29266; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Shipwrecks Index [Folders 10-11 of 11])
    - On The Road, Charles Kuralt with Aycock Brown, British Cemetery, Ocracoke [audiocassette], 6 June 1994; 190716; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item On The Road, Charles Kuralt with Aycock Brown, British Cemetery, Ocracoke [audiocassette])
    - Origin of Names in the Outer Banks of North Carolina / Pilot's Guide to the Outer Banks, undated; 29267; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Origin of Names in the Outer Banks of North Carolina / Pilot's Guide to the Outer Banks)
    - Outer Banks Dupes, undated; 29268; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Outer Banks Dupes)
    - Perry, Oliver L. Sr., Nansemond Indians, 1987; 29269; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Perry, Oliver L. Sr., Nansemond Indians)
    - Portsmouth Village, 1991; 29270; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Portsmouth Village)
    - Post Office Histories, undated; 29271; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Post Office Histories)
    - Report on the S.S. Merida from Records in the Foul Anchor Archives, 1955-1956; 29272; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Report on the S.S. Merida from Records in the Foul Anchor Archives)
    - Research Letters, 1959; 29273; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Letters)
    - Research Notes, Letters, etc., 1955-1966; 29274; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Notes, Letters, etc.)
    - Roads and Highways, 1951-1964; 29275; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roads and Highways)
    - Run Hill, 1992; 29276; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Run Hill)
    - Rural Electrification in North Carolina, 1963; 29277; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rural Electrification in North Carolina)
    - Sermon by Dr. Arthur M. Aucock, 1956; 29278; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sermon by Dr. Arthur M. Aucock)
    - Shackleford Banks Ponies, 1996-1998; 29279; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Shackleford Banks Ponies)
    - Southern Shores, circa 1950s-1970s; 29280; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Southern Shores)
    - Talcott Williams Survey (1896) and J.C. Harrington Survey (1962) Coordinates, undated; 29281; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Talcott Williams Survey (1896) and J.C. Harrington Survey (1962) Coordinates)
    - Tatham, William - Original Report on the Survey of the Coast of North Carolina (1806) [3 Folders], 1982-1984 and undated; 29282; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Tatham, William - Original Report on the Survey of the Coast of North Carolina (1806) [3 Folders])
    - Thornbury, Les, 1970s; 29283; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Coastal Effluent, etc., 1970s; 39370; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Effluent, etc.)
      - Currituck Project Miscellaneous, 1970s; 39371; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Currituck Project Miscellaneous)
      - General, 1972; 39372; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder General)
      - Mew Water Recreation, 1970s; 39373; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Mew Water Recreation)
      - Miscellaneous Notes and Correspondence, 1970s; 39374; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Notes and Correspondence)
      - Septic Tanks, 1970s; 39375; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Septic Tanks)
      - Other Papers, 1970s; 39376; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Other Papers)
    - Unidentified Research Materials, undated; 29284; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Unidentified Research Materials)
    - Various Papers on Shellfish Landings, Finfish Landings, Crabmeat Picking, and Shrimp Landings, 1971; 29285; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Various Papers on Shellfish Landings, Finfish Landings, Crabmeat Picking, and Shrimp Landings)
    - Water Quality, 1996-1997; 29286; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Water Quality)
    - Wreck of the Barkentine Vera Cruz VII, 1950; 29287; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wreck of the Barkentine Vera Cruz VII)
    - Wright Brothers - Wright Memorial, 1985; 29288; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Brothers - Wright Memorial)
  - Clippings, circa 1780-2002 and undated; 6735; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    The Clippings subseries, circa 1780-2002 and undated, contains clippings taken by Stick from newspapers and articles related to various topics of interest to him. Some clippings are mounted on scrapbook pages, and many clippings are photocopies. A number of the files in this subseries contain clippings related to organizations and agencies with which Stick was affiliated (original records related to these entities can be found in the Organizations and Agencies series of this collection).
    - America's Four Hundredth Anniversary Committee, 1982-1986; 7117; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Archaeology - Chowanoke, 1983; 29289; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archaeology - Chowanoke)
      - Archaeology - Ft. Raleigh, 1982-1985; 29290; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archaeology - Ft. Raleigh)
      - Archaeology - Miscellaneous, 1983-1986; 29291; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archaeology - Miscellaneous)
      - Archaeology - Pomeiok, 1985-1986; 29292; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archaeology - Pomeiok)
      - Archaeology - Underwater, 1984-1986; 29293; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archaeology - Underwater)
      - Publications, 1984-1985; 29294; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Publications)
    - Archaeology, 1950-1972; 29295; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Archaeology)
    - Ash Wednesday Storm, 1962; 29296; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ash Wednesday Storm)
    - Ash Wednesday Storm Inlet, 1962-1963; 29297; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Ash Wednesday Storm Inlet)
    - Bald Head and Cape Fear, 1955; 29298; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Bald Head and Cape Fear)
    - Beach Buggies, 1978; 29299; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Beach Buggies)
    - Beach Ponies, 1978; 29300; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Beach Ponies)
    - Birds, 1949-1989; 29301; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Birds)
    - Boating (Recreational), 1983; 29302; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Boating (Recreational))
    - Bridges, 1926-1983; 29303; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Bridges)
    - Buses, 1948; 29304; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Buses)